Guide to the Paul A. Samuelson papers, 1933-2010 and undated RL.10082
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1960-2009
  - Economics Cassette Series: Paul Samuelson, 1969-1977; 1
    - Tape 111 - International monetary bank and fund, 1972 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0109)
    - Tape 112 - Review of IMF actions, 1972 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0110)
    - Tape 113 - Credit crunch in 1973, 1972 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0111)
    - Tape 114 - Political economics after the elections, assuming..., 1972 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0112)
    - Tape 115 - The Dow Jones tops 1,000, 1972 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0113)
    - Tape 116 - Economic outlook for 1973, 1972 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0114)
    - Tape 117 - Influence of Professor Milton Friedman; what a difference a month makes, 1972 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0115)
    - Tape 118 - Economic Forecasts Roundup; Wall Street, 1972 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0116)
    - Tape 119 - The meaning of phase III, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0117)
    - Tape 120 - Presidential economics: comparative review, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0118)
    - Tape 121 - Presidents messages; unemployment; phase III, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0119)
    - Tape 122 - Devaluation of the Dollar, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0120)
    - Tape 123 - More on the Dollar Crisis; the domestic outlook, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0121)
    - Tape 125 - A look at Japan, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0122)
    - Tape 126 - Overheating of the economy and that money crunch, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0123)
    - Tape 127 - Answers to listeners questions, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0124)
    - Tape 128 - Analysis of recent international money market activity, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0125)
    - Tape 129 - GNP; interest rates; stock market, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0126)
    - Tape 130 - Phase 3 1/2, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0127)
    - Tape 131 - Mid-year turnaround?, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0128)
    - Tape 132 - Watergate; the money crunch, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0129)
    - Tape 133 - Supporting the dollar; monetarism; US on the bargain block, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0130)
    - Tape 135 - Recession ahead, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0131)
    - Tape 136 - The new business year begins, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0132)
    - Tape 137 - Worldwide inflation, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0133)
    - Tape 139 - Leontief's nobel award; world GNP and US eclipse, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0134)
    - Tape 140 - Third period GNP; soft landing?, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0135)
    - Tape 142 - More on the energy crisis, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0136)
    - Tape 143 - Economic outlook for 1974, 1973 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0137)
    - Tape 144 - Lessons from recent economic history, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0138)
    - Tape 146 - On the state of the union address, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0139)
    - Tape 147 - The president's economic report, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0140)
    - Tape 148 - Runaway inflation; gradual recovery, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0141)
    - Tape 149 - How to invest lesson #1: stocks versus non-stocks; diversified piece of whole market, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0142)
    - Tape 150 - Springtime upturn?, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0143)
    - Tape 152 - Longtime erosion of profits, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0144)
    - Tape 153 - Re-analysis of first quarter figures, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0145)
    - Tape 160 - Ford's middle road, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0146)
    - Tape 159 - Stock predictions and money, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0147)
    - Tape 158 - Mid-year guessing's, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0148)
    - Tape 157 - The future revealed, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0149)
    - Tape 156 - Cheerful food outlook; how European funds perform, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0150)
    - Tape 155 - Economics in crisis, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0151)
    - Tape 162 - Economist meet at the summit, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0152)
    - Tape 161 - Challenge to investment judgment, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0153)
    - Tape 165 - The noble laureates, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0154)
    - Tape 168 - Economic outlook for 1975, circa 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0155)
    - Tape 169 - Consensus of year- end forecasts, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0156)
    - Tape 164 - Somber autumn outlook, 1974 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0157)
    - Tape 173 - The depression of 1975, or recession? (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0158)
    - Tape 176 - Social security and tax egalitarianism, 1975 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0159)
    - Tape 177 - Will the federal deficit crowd out private financing, 1975 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0160)
    - Tape 178 - New economic doctrines, 1975 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0161)
    - Tape 179 - Crowding out effect of Deficit?, 1975 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0162)
    - Tape 180 - Waiting for Godot and recovery, 1975 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0163)
    - Tape 181 - The turn...at last!, 1975 June (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0164)
    - Tape 183 - Outlook at midyear, 1975 July (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0165)
    - Tape 184 - World growth to 2000 A.D., 1975 July (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0166)
    - Tape 185 - Forecast for recovery, 1975 August (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0167)
    - Tape 186 - Fuel, food, inflation, 1975 August (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0168)
    - Tape 187 - In search of an energy policy, 1975 September (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0185)
    - Tape 188 - Assessing the recovery, 1975 October (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0169)
    - Tape 189 - 1975 Nobel Award, 1975 October (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0170)
    - Tape 190 - The assessment of the business trend, 1975 October (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0171)
    - Tape 191 - The economic summit, 1975 November (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0172)
    - Tape 193 - State of the Union, 1976 February (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0173)
    - Tape 194 - The course of the recovery, 1976 February (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0174)
    - Tape 195 - The 200th anniversary of Adam Smith's "The Wealth of Nations", 1976 February (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0175)
    - Tape 196 - Commentary on Friedman's income tax ceiling; state and gift taxes; distribution of wealth; President's tax reform, 1976 April (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0176)
    - Tape 197 - U.S. economy; latest GNP; inflation prospects; interest rates; favorable stock market analysis, 1976 April (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0177)
    - Tape 198 - International economic picture-Britain, Switzerland, Italy, Japan; U.S. and expenditures for poor nations, 1976 May (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0178)
    - Tape 199 - Gold-IMF auction; potato futures; visit to the White House and the economy; recession 1978?, 1976 June (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0179)
    - Tape 200 - Jimmy Carter: presidential prospects, economic advisors, economic positions, background, 1976 June (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0180)
    - Tape 201 - Rescue of British Pound; U.S. economic recovery slows; 1 1/2 cheers for Ford; Fed restrains money growth, 1976 June (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0181)
    - Tape 203 - REITs and banks; Jimmy Carter as President; the slow-down in GNP; the Humphrey-Hawkins Bill, 1976 July (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0182)
    - Tape 206 - Western Europe; poor Britain-an endangered "snake"; a solid German mark; shaky French economy, 1976 October (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0183)
    - Tape 208 - Friedman's Nobel Prize; GNP growth slows; inflation down; final sales up; mystery in federal spending, 1976 October (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0184)
    - Tape 209 - Problems for Jimmy Carter; a tough Arthur Burns; a Democratic Fed; Carter appointments, 1976 November (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0186)
    - Tape 210 - Jimmy Carter's economic goal for 1977; Fed plays politics; need for tax cut; the missing billions, 1976 November (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0187)
    - Tape 212 - Economy picks up; OPEC price boost; Carter's economic appointees, 1976 December (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0188)
    - Tape 214 - GNP figures; price outlook; the economic summit; third world debts, 1977 January (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0189)
    - Tape 215 - Cold weather and the economy; independence of the Federal Reserve System, 1977 February (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0190)
    - Tape 216 - Bad news on inflation and GNP; Carter's first budget; Congress and the Fed, 1977 February (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0191)
    - untitled, circa 1971-1972 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0192)
  - Economics Cassette Series: Milton Friedman, 1968-1977; 2
    - Tape 001 - untitled, circa 1968 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0193)
    - Tape 002 - untitled, circa 1968 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0194)
    - Tape 003 - untitled, circa 1968 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0195)
    - Tape 004 - untitled, circa 1968 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0196)
    - Tape 005 - untitled, circa 1968 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0197)
    - Tape 006 - untitled, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0198)
    - Tape 007 - untitled, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0199)
    - Tape 008 - untitled, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0200)
    - Tape 009 - 1969 forecast; new administration policies; surtax possibilities (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0201)
    - Tape 010 - 1969 forecast amplification; decrease in growth rate of monetary supply (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0202)
    - Tape 011 - The 10 Percent Surtax, the 1969 Economic Report, Is a New Crisis Coming? (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0203)
    - Tape 012 - Exchange Rates and Imports, Monetary Versus Fiscal Policy, Measures of Monetary Policy, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0204)
    - Tape 013 - Second Half of 1969: slowdown Foreseen, Money/Cause or Effect (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0205)
    - Tape 014 - New Bretton Woods Would Be Disaster, Monetary Policy Article in New York Times, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0206)
    - Tape 015 - Conglomerates, Tax Reform, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0207)
    - Tape 016 - Divergent Monetary Trends, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0208)
    - Tape 017 - British Bank Rate, French Revolution, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0209)
    - Tape 018 - Current Monetary News, Conservative Disappointment with Nixon, 3, Independence of Federal Reserve, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0210)
    - Tape 019 - Monetary Developments, Demand and Supply of Money and Credits, Inflation and Unemployment, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0211)
    - Tape 020 - Current Monetary and Economic Developments, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0212)
    - Tape 021 - International Financial Picture: Reduction of United States Exchange Controls, Credit Restraint Euro-Dollars, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0213)
    - Tape 022 - Current Monetary Developments: Prospects for Interest Rates, Nixon Budget, Peace Rumors and the Market Federal Funds Rate, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0214)
    - Tape 023 - Nixon's Tax Proposals, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0215)
    - Tape 024 - Reaction to Samuelson: Impact of De Gaulle's Resignation, Effect on US Dollar, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0216)
    - Tape 025 - Monetary Policy, Gold Prices, Vietnam Peace, Investment Tax Credit, 'Collectivism', 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0217)
    - Tape 026 - Current Monetary Indication, Balance of Payments Deficit, Rush for German Marks, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0218)
    - Tape 027 - Businessmen and Inflation, Bond Market, Harry Schultz Letter, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0219)
    - Tape 028 - Money Supply, Pressure for Rate Increase, David Kennedy and Wage and Price Controls, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0220)
    - Tape 029 - Current Conditions, A.B.A. International Monetary Conference, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0221)
    - Tape 030 - Monetary Developments, Interest Rates, Compensating Balances and Interest on Demand Deposits, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0222)
    - Tape 031 - Quantity of Money, Behavior of Interest Rates, Real vs. Nominal Interest Rates, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0223)
    - Tape 032 - Monetary Developments, Future Federal Policy Lag in Effect of Money, Tax Legislation, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0224)
    - Tape 033 - Nixon Welfare Proposal, Revision of Money Supply Figures, Subscribers' Questions, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0225)
    - Tape 034 - Japan, Current Economic Conditions, Overkill, Interest Deduction, Capital Gains, Rediscounting, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0226)
    - Tape 035 - Unemployment Figures, Monetary Developments, Interest Rates, Economic Forecast, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0227)
    - Tape 036 - Appointment of Arthur Burns to Fed, German Mark and Exchange Rates, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0228)
    - Tape 037 - Monetary Developments, Economic Development, Cost of Anti-Inflation, Production / Property Taxes, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0229)
    - Tape 038 - Monetary Developments, Interest Rates, Rinfret's Predictions, Stock Market, Bank Holding Co. Comm. Paper, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0230)
    - Tape 040 - Monetary Developments, Feasibility of Steady Monetary Growth, Rinfret's Predictions, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0231)
    - Tape 041 - Prospective Money Situation, Velority Behavior, 1969 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0232)
    - Tape 042 - Nixon Reaction to Recession, Wage Settlements and Unemployment, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0233)
    - Tape 043 - Money Stock, Regulation Question, Pollution, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0234)
    - Tape 044 - Bond Market Turn, Debt, Bankruptcies, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0235)
    - Tape 045 - Economic Trends, Money and Bonds, Vounteer Armed Forces, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0236)
    - Tape 046 - Economic and Monetary Conditions, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0237)
    - Tape 047 - Japan and Korea, Monetary Developments, Economic Developments, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0238)
    - Tape 048 - Income Tax, Econometric Models, Canada vs. U.S. in Cost Depression, Pollution, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0239)
    - Tape 049 - General Economic Conditions, Market Price Increases, Margin Requirements on Stocks, Liquidity Crisis, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0240)
    - Tape 050 - Stock Market, Is This 1929, Low Point of Current Revision, Subscribers Questions, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0241)
    - Tape 051 - Stock Market, Credit Crisis, Monetary Policy, Income Policy, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0242)
    - Tape 052 - Distinctive Features of Recession, High Interest Rates, Control of Money Supply, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0243)
    - Tape 053 - Penn Central Bankruptcy, Monetary Development, President Nixon's Economic Sale, Subscribers' Questions, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0244)
    - Tape 054 - Monetary Development, Interest Rates/Money Supply, British Tax Policy, Debt Liquidation/Dollar, Devaluation/Black Angus, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0245)
    - Tape 055 - Inflation, Bottoming of Economy, Interest Rates, Capital Spending, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0246)
    - Tape 056 - Monetary Developments, Bottoming of Recession, Long Term Interest Rates, Recommended Money Supply, Real Money Supply, Jewish Conspiracy, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0247)
    - Tape 056 - Monetary Developments, Bottoming of Recession, Long Term Interest Rates, Recommended Money Supply, Real Money Supply, Jewish Conspiracy, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0248)
    - Tape 057 - General Review of Outlook for Money, Business, Inflation, Stock Market, Interest Rates, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0249)
    - Tape 058 - Monetary and Economic Conditions, Commentary on Britain and Italy, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0250)
    - Tape 059 - Current Economic Condition, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0251)
    - Tape 060 - Pre-Election Economic Perspective, Real Money Supply, Residual Money Supply, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0252)
    - Tape 061 - Industrial Production Decline, Monetary Development, Fed Policy, Subscribers Questions, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0253)
    - Tape 062 - Implications of Monetary Development, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0254)
    - Tape 063 - Outlook for 1971, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0255)
    - Tape 064 - Economic Development, Constructive Money, Growth, 1970 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0256)
    - Tape 065 - Monetary Developments, Depreciation Liberalization, Steel Prices, 1971 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0257)
    - Tape 066 - Monetary Figures, Steel Prices Ploy, State of Union Message, 1971 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0258)
    - Tape 067 - Administration Projections, Projected Default, 1971 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0259)
    - Tape 068 - Davis Bacon Act, Forecasts, Band Market, Common Market Currency, 1971 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0260)
    - Tape 069 - Monetary Development, Bond Market, Budget, Escalated Bond, 1971 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0261)
    - Tape 070 - S.S.T., Oil Import Quotas, Interest Rates, 1971 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0262)
    - Tape 071 - Monetary Developments, Living with Inflation, 1971 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0263)
    - Tape 072 - Monetary Development, Stock market, GNP Growth, National Dividend Plan, 1971 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0264)
    - Tape 074 - International Monetary Developments, Domestic Recovery, 1971 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0265)
    - Tape 075 - Interest Rates and Money, Subscribers Questions, 1971 June 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0266)
    - Tape 076 - Time's Board of Economists, St. Louis Price Predictions, Cost-Push-Inflation, 1971 June 15 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0267)
    - Tape 078 - Mr. Nixon's Policy, Unemployment, Effect of Monetary Changes, Inflation Potential, 1971 July (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0268)
    - Tape 079 - Monetary Development, Monetarist Forecasts, Seasonal Adjustment of Money, Balance of Payment, 1971 July 27 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0269)
    - Tape 080 - Unilateral Devaluation of Dollar, Speculation for the Yen Inflation, 1971 August (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0270)
    - Tape 081 - The President's New Economic Policy, 1971 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0271)
    - Tape 082 - International Monetary Development, Domestic Economy, 1971 September 27 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0272)
    - Tape 087 - Forecast for 1972, 1971 December 1 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0273)
    - Tape 089 - Have Monetary Policies Failed? Monetary and International Developments, 1971 December 26 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0274)
    - Tape 091 - Deficits, GNP Estimates, Money, Subscriber's Questions, 1972 January 26 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0275)
    - Tape 107 - European Fear of Inflation, US Monetary Developments, Flood Relief, Gold, 1972 September 20 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0276)
    - Tape 112 - Economic Outlook for 1973, 1972 November 29 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0277)
    - Tape 116 - International Monetary Crisis, Domestic Monetary Growth, 1973 March 5 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0278)
    - Tape 117 - Yugoslavia, International Monetary Development, 1973 March 14 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0279)
    - Tape 118 - Report on Yugoslavia and Italy, 1973 April 13 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0280)
    - Tape 119 - Inflations, Monetary Development, Prospects, 1973 April 25 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0281)
    - Tape 120 - Discount Rate, Current Boom, Future Prospects, Balance of Payments, 1973 May 11 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0282)
    - Tape 121 - Gold and the Dollar, Stock Market, Wage and Price Controls, 1973 May 24 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0283)
    - Tape 122 - Adam Smith, Controls, Dollar and Gold, Watergate and the Economy, 1973 June 11 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0284)
    - Tape 124 - The German Mark, Federal Reserve Action, Interest Rates, Subscribers Queries, 1973 July 4 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0285)
    - Tape 138 - Economic Conditions, Monetary policy, International Scene, Watergate and Resignation, 1974 January 16 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0286)
    - Tape 140 - Personal Income and Wholesale Prices, Real Money Balances, Monetary Correction, 1974 February 20 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0287)
    - Tape 142 - President Nixon, Money, Inflation, 1974 March 20 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0288)
    - Tape 144 - Money, Disintermediation, Thrift Institutions, Inflation Prospects, 1974 April 17 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0289)
    - Tape 145 - Money Figures and Fed Stand, Nixon-Burns Forecast about Food/Fuel "Bubble Burst Effect", 1974 May 1 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0290)
    - Tape 146 - Franklin National, Flexible Exchange Rates, Ideas vs. Experience, 1974 May 20 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0291)
    - Tape 147 - Monetary Policy, Burns Talk, Leading Indicators, Wage Price Controls, 1974 March 30 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0292)
    - Tape 149 - Current Economic Conditions, Capital Markets, Indexation Stock Volume and Prices, 1974 June 26 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0293)
    - Tape 150 - Alan Greenspan, Monetary Growth, Recession? Bank Failures, 1974 July 24 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0294)
    - Tape 151 - Implications of Prospective End of Nixon Presidency, Retrospective on Nixon Years, Commercial and Industrial Loans, 1974 August 7 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0295)
    - Tape 152 - Monetary Policy, Economic Prospects, GM and Ford Price Hikes, Price and Wage Controls?, 1974 August 21 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0296)
    - Tape 155 - President Ford's Message, 1974 October 10 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0297)
    - Tape 156 - Prospects for Inflation, Business Conditions, Interest rates, British Election, 1974 October 23 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0298)
    - Tape 157 - Election Consequences, Media, Money Supply, 1974 November 6 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0299)
    - Tape 159 - Economic Outlook for 1975, 1974 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0300)
    - Tape 160 - Steel Prices, Personal Income, Money and Prices, Administration Policy, 1974 December 19 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0301)
    - Tape 165 - Reader's Questions, Oil Cartel, 1975 February (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0302)
    - Tape 167 - Domestic Economy, Vacuum in Far East, Chile Inflation, 1975 May (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0303)
    - Tape 173 - Monetary Policy, Wheat Sale, Oil Decontrol, Kelso, 1975 August (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0304)
    - Tape 174 - Inflation, Federal Debt, Anemic Expansion, 1975 August (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0305)
    - Tape 175 - Money, Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco, Monetary Targets, Eurodollars, 1975 September (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL10082-CS-0306)